(Sheldon:)to find out how he was being
perceived by his subjects.
Of course, if he'd
(Sheldon:)have read any
of the 1,300 e-mails
(Sheldon:)I've sent him on the subject
of his administration,
(Sheldon:)he could have saved himself
the trouble.
(Raj:)Or maybe he heard it's
Tator Tot Tuesday.
(Raj:)That's why I'm here.
(Dr. Seibert:)Hey, there's
my favorite geniuses!
(Dr. Seibert:)How are we doing today?
(Sheldon:)That depends--
how much longer
(Sheldon:)do you plan on
fondling my shoulder?
(Seibert:)Sorry, Dr. Cooper, I forgot
you have a touch phobia.
(Sheldon:)It's not a touch phobia,
it's a germ phobia.
(Sheldon:)If you'd like to go put on
a pair of latex gloves,
I'll let you check me
for a hernia.
(Raj:)Yeah.
(Seibert:)So, listen, fellas, who's up
for a little party this Saturday night?
(Seibert:)Open bar, good eats, might
even be a few pretty girls.
(Raj:)Sounds great!
I'm in!
(Sheldon:)Hold on.
(Sheldon:)Just because the nice man
is offering you candy,
(Sheldon:)doesn't mean you should jump
into his windowless van.
(Sheldon:)What's the occasion?
(Seibert:)Just a little fund-raiser
for the university.
(Sheldon:)Aha! The tear-stained air
mattress in the back of the van.
(Seibert:)I understand
your reticence, Dr. Cooper,